A Guide to the Joseph Francis Fletcher Papers (1931-1991)
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- William H. Matchett to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 13 (Box-folder 007:038)
- Kenneth Curtis to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 14 (Box-folder 007:039)
- Mrs. L. Bodtker to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 16 (Box-folder 007:040)
- Edward L. Rich, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 19 (Box-folder 007:041)
- Edward A. White to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 19 (Box-folder 007:042)
- Donald J. Campbell to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 23 (Box-folder 007:043)
- Richard F. Hettlinger to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 September 23 (Box-folder 007:044)
- Kenneth D. Jordan to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 September 27 (Box-folder 007:045)
- Thomas J. Fleming to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 6 (Box-folder 007:046)
- Charles L. Ammons to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 Ocotber 12 (Box-folder 007:047)
- Charles m. Guilbert to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 13 (Box-folder 007:048)
- Sherwin T. Wine and Mrs. Avram Rosenthal to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 15 (Box-folder 007:049)
- Braxton H. Tabb, Jr. to Robert F. Gibson, Jr., with a note by Tabb to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 17 (Box-folder 007:050)
- John Lachs to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosed manuscript, 1966 October 20, 2 Items (Box-folder 007:051)
- James A. Davis to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 21 (Box-folder 007:052)
- Carol A. Fischler to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 24 (Box-folder 007:053)
- George E. Ross to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 25 (Box-folder 007:054)
- William M. Todd to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 26 (Box-folder 007:055)
- Philip L. Quandt to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 27 (Box-folder 007:056)
- Stan Reynolds to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 27 (Box-folder 007:057)
- Henry G. Pearson to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 October 30 (Box-folder 007:058)
- Seward to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 October (Box-folder 007:059)
- JF [Joseph Fletcher] to Forrest Fletcher, 1966 November 2 (Box-folder 007:060)
- Alice Kermeen to Joseph Fletcher, and other materials related to Fletcher's appearance at this conference, 1966 November 3 - [1967] January 13, 3 Items (Box-folder 007:061)
- F. Randall Williams to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 8 (Box-folder 007:062)
- Greer McClellan Taylor to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 10 (Box-folder 007:063)
- Elmore C. Young to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 November 10 (Box-folder 007:064)
- Charles D. Eslinger to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 11 (Box-folder 007:065)
- Henry Bird to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 November 12 (Box-folder 007:066)
- Nancy Thompson to [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 November 13 (Box-folder 007:067)
- Henlee H. Barnette to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 14 (Box-folder 007:068)
- Artley Parson to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1966] November 14 (Box-folder 007:069)
- Erville Waynaed(?) to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 November 14 (Box-folder 007:070)
- Don R. Francis to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 15 (Box-folder 007:071)
- Stuart Huckins to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 15 (Box-folder 007:072)
- Alsen D. Kelley to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 November 15 (Box-folder 007:073)
- Florence Mair to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 15 (Box-folder 007:074)
- Donald N. Sweeny, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 15 (Box-folder 007:075)
- Clara Williams to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 15 (Box-folder 007:076)
- Anonymous to Joseph Fletcher, with additional printed materials, 1966 November 15, 8 Items (Box-folder 007:077)
- Leah Babcock to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 16 (Box-folder 007:078)
- Bette Lees Bemis to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 16 (Box-folder 007:079)
- Geerhardus Vos to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 17 (Box-folder 007:080)
- Louise M. Jackson to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 18 (Box-folder 007:081)
- James Quitter to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 18 (Box-folder 007:082)
- Roddy to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1966 November 21 (Box-folder 007:083)
- Jerome J. Fussell to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 22 (Box-folder 007:084)
- Blanche Leak Gluyas to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 22 (Box-folder 007:085)
- Herb Reece to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 22 (Box-folder 007:086)
- Robert E. Hall to Joseph Fletcher, with note by Fletcher to Ruth Proskauer Smith, 1966 November 23 (Box-folder 007:087)
- Wilfred Myll to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 23 (Box-folder 007:087)
- Stewart C. Broom, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1966 November 25 (Box-folder 007:088)
- Austin Wane to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 25 (Box-folder 007:089)
- Gleb Botkin to Joseph Fletcher, with attachments, 1966 November 26, 4 Items (Box-folder 007:090)
- Albert Edge to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 26 (Box-folder 007:091)
- Blanche Leak Gluyas to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 28 (Box-folder 007:092)
- Wilma Hopkins to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 28 (Box-folder 007:093)
- Alder T. Root to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 November 28 (Box-folder 007:094)
- Bill Cross to Joe and Forrest [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher], [1966? November] (Box-folder 007:095)
- Robert E. Fitch to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1966 December 3 (Box-folder 007:096)
- Franchot Buhler to [Wilfred Myll], 1966 December 5 (Box-folder 007:097)
- Delle C. Dale to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 December 5 (Box-folder 007:098)
- Melvin E. Greer to [Wilfred] Myll, 1966 December 5 (Box-folder 007:099)
- John T. Loftus to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 December 6 (Box-folder 007:100)
- William R. Johnson to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 December 8 (Box-folder 007:101)
- S. Burman Long to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 December 8 (Box-folder 007:102)
- Howard R. Burkle to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 December 9 (Box-folder 007:103)
- Frank Elliott to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 December 9 (Box-folder 007:104)
- Ronald E. Keener to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 December 24 (Box-folder 007:105)
- M. A. Kemp to KTTV Television Station, Alan Burke Show, 1966 December 29 (Box-folder 007:106)
- Douglas T. Holden to Joseph Fletcher, 1966 December 31 (Box-folder 007:107)
- Lecture Announcement, St. Martin's-in-the-Fields, Philadelphia, 1966 December (Box-folder 007:108)
- Mrs. J. S. Crislip to Joseph Fletcher, [1966] (Box-folder 007:109)
- Wilford O. Cross to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1966?] (Box-folder 007:110)
- Joseph Fletcher, Conference I.D. Card, World Conference on Church and Society, 1966 (Box-folder 007:111)
- John Graham to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1966] (Box-folder 007:112)
- Mary Ginion(?) Harry to Joseph Fletcher, [1966] (Box-folder 007:113)
- C. W. Kirkpatrick to [Joseph Fletcher], [1966] (Box-folder 007:114)
- George C. Powell to [Joseph Fletcher], [1966] (Box-folder 007:115)
- Suncook School of Christian Education Flyer, [1966] (Box-folder 007:116)
- Ingegerd Uppman to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, [1966], 3 Items (Box-folder 007:117)
- Mrs. Ande[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, [1966] (Box-folder 007:118)
- Anonymous to Joseph Fletcher, [1966] (Box-folder 007:119)
- Joseph Fletcher Lecture Schedule, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 007:120)
- Andrew H. Newman to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 3 (Box-folder 008:001)
- Herbert P. Carroll to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 4 (Box-folder 008:002)
- Bernice Small to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 4 (Box-folder 008:003)
- Helen S. Braid to [Allan] Burke, 1967 January 5, 3 Items (Box-folder 008:004)
- Thomas W. Gibbs to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 5 (Box-folder 008:005)
- Albert Di Ianni to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 6 (Box-folder 008:006)
- Herbert A. Kenny to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 6 (Box-folder 008:007)
- Masume Grace Kodama to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1967 January 6 (Box-folder 008:008)
- William L. Klug to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 7 (Box-folder 008:009)
- Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 7 (Box-folder 008:010)
- Mollie Bolten to Forrest Fletcher, 1967 January 13 (Box-folder 008:011)
- Harriet Bradley to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 13 (Box-folder 008:012)
- Edward J. Tucker to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 16 (Box-folder 008:013)
- Steven Cole to Joseph Fletcher, with attached paper, 1967 January 17, 2 Items (Box-folder 008:014)
- Sara Orton to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 18 (Box-folder 008:015)
- Richard Smith to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] January 18 (Box-folder 008:016)
- Materials related to the Young Presidents' Organization, Aspen Seminar, 1967 January 22-27, 11 Items (Box-folder 008:017)
- M. Ando to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 25 (Box-folder 008:018)
- Materials related to the Episcopal Theological School Centennial Convocation, a conference on theological education as professional education, 1967 January 27-29, May 2, 23 Items (Box-folder 008:019)
- Judith A. Melicks to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 January 31 (Box-folder 008:020)
- Harold S. Williams to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, 1967 January 31, 4 Items (Box-folder 008:021)
- Patti Bruning to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 1 (Box-folder 008:022)
- Bob [Robert Gittleman] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 February 2 (Box-folder 008:023)
- Reed Engle to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 5 (Box-folder 008:024)
- Robert Gittleman to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 6 (Box-folder 008:025)
- Janic F. Putnam to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 8 (Box-folder 008:026)
- E. B. Young to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 12 (Box-folder 008:027)
- Agnes Duff to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 13 (Box-folder 008:028)
- Joseph Fletcher to John B. Coburn, 1967 February 13 (Box-folder 008:029)
- Editors, Catholic Action Federations to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 14 (Box-folder 008:030)
- Dolly Jackson to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 February 14 (Box-folder 008:031)
- Mary Kate Davis to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1967 February 15, 3 Items (Box-folder 008:032)
- James R. Mac Coll III to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 16 (Box-folder 008:033)
- [Paul L. Meacham] to Joseph Fletcher, (incomplete letter) 1967 February 16 (Box-folder 008:034)
- Linda Brackin to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 17 (Box-folder 008:035)
- Alfred C. Roller to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 17 (Box-folder 008:036)
- Alice Kermeen to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 19 (Box-folder 008:037)
- Gerald D. Brittle to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 20 (Box-folder 008:038)
- Ed White to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 February 20 (Box-folder 008:039)
- Memorandum to Faculty, Episcopal Theological School, 1967 March 8 (Box-folder 008:040)
- Roy Culhane to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, 1967 March 11 (Box-folder 008:041)
- Dick Preston to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1967?] March 17 (Box-folder 008:042)
- Thomas A. Roach to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure and note from [Joseph Fletcher] to Tom[ ] with response, 1967 March 23, 3 Items (Box-folder 008:043)
- Virginia Henckel to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 March 24 (Box-folder 008:044)
- James D. Hansen to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 3 (Box-folder 008:045)
- Frederick M. Brooks to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 6 (Box-folder 008:046)
- Mrs. John L. Strohm to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 6 (Box-folder 008:047)
- Laura Bartholomew to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 7 (Box-folder 008:048)
- Lyman Covert to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 10 (Box-folder 008:049)
- K. N. S. Counter to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 11 (Box-folder 008:050)
- Emma Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 14 (Box-folder 008:051)
- William Cory to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1967 April 14, 2 Items (Box-folder 008:052)
- Materials concerning the conference "Mortality for Man Today," the Open School, Church of the Redeemer, Baltimore, Maryland, 1967 April 14, 15 (Box-folder 008:053)
- Mark G. Knight to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 19 (Box-folder 008:054)
- Ralph E. Flanders to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 24 (Box-folder 008:055)
- James D. Hansen to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 24 (Box-folder 008:056)
- Robert M.Waugh to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 24 (Box-folder 008:057)
- A. H. Constant to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 25 (Box-folder 008:058)
- Paul L. Meacham to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 26 (Box-folder 008:059)
- Harvey Moore to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 26 (Box-folder 008:060)
- Lloyd D.Doyle to [Joseph Fletcher], and Fletcher's response to Doyle, 1967 April 27, May 8, 2 Items (Box-folder 008:061)
- "Fletcher Plays Leading Role at Mayo Clinic Conference," 1967 April 27 (Box-folder 008:062)
- Max Ballas to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 April 28 (Box-folder 008:063)
- Clarence Levi Shelby to [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 April 29 (Box-folder 008:064)
- Ralph E. Flanders to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 1 (Box-folder 008:065)
- Billy Wolfe to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 1 (Box-folder 008:066)
- Rory M. Culhane to Joseph Fletcher, and Fletcher's response to Culhane, 1967 May 3, 8 (Box-folder 008:067)
- Edward C. Tarte to Joseph Fletcher, and Fletcher's response to Tarte, 1967 May 3, 8 (Box-folder 008:068)
- Joseph Fletcher to Francis Caswell, 1967 May 8 (Box-folder 008:069)
- Mrs. S. Don Wilson to [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 May 8 (Box-folder 008:070)
- Brian Templeton to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 9 (Box-folder 008:071)
- Melissa Woelfel to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosed letter of Jim Woelfel to Mr. Davidson, 1967 May 9 (Box-folder 008:072)
- Eugene A. Confrey to Leon R. Lezer, 1967 May 10 (Box-folder 008:073)
- Helen Zaiser to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 10 (Box-folder 008:074)
- Diane to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 10 (Box-folder 008:075)
- Ben[jamin] B. Page to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosed manuscript, [1967] May 11, 2 Items (Box-folder 008:076)
- Martin Gal[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 15 (Box-folder 008:077)
- Wirt Barnitz to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 16 (Box-folder 008:078)
- Paul M. Van Buren to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 May 17 (Box-folder 008:079)
- D. Peter Burrows to the editor, "The South Bay Daily Breeze," 1967 May 19 (Box-folder 008:080)
- F[rank?] Rubel to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 22 (Box-folder 008:081)
- Norman Ross to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 23 (Box-folder 008:082)
- Ralph A. Deterling, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 24 (Box-folder 008:083)
- Herbert E. Wigle to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 May 29 (Box-folder 008:084)
- Dale A. hawley to Joseph Fletcher, and Fletcher's response to Hawley [1967 May], 1967 May 8, 2 Items (Box-folder 008:085)
- Charles A. M. Hall to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 5 (Box-folder 008:086)
- P. E. A. Addo to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 8 (Box-folder 008:087)
- Murray H. L[ ] to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 10 (Box-folder 008:088)
- Anonymous to [Joseph] Fletcher, with envelope, 1967 June 14 (Box-folder 008:089)
- George N. Morris to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 18 (Box-folder 008:090)
- Margeret Proferbel to Rene L. Paquette, and Paquette's response to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] June 18, N.D. (Box-folder 008:091)
- Isabel Trend(?) to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 18 (Box-folder 008:092)
- William H. Marmion to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 19 (Box-folder 008:093)
- Warren C. Propes to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 20 (Box-folder 008:094)
- Betty Steadman to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 25 (Box-folder 008:095)
- Warren C. Propes to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 26 (Box-folder 008:096)
- William B. Eerdmans, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, with two enclosures, 1967 June 29, 3 Items (Box-folder 008:097)
- Harry Lee Doll to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 30 (Box-folder 008:098)
- Elaine Nussbaum to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 June 30 (Box-folder 008:099)
- Benjamin B. Page to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] July 8 (Box-folder 009:001)
- Madeline Gray to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 July 17 (Box-folder 009:002)
- Jean K. Read to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 July 20 (Box-folder 009:003)
- Jeffrey Kittredge to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 July 22 (Box-folder 009:004)
- Alma Roberts to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 July 24 (Box-folder 009:005)
- Ford Wright, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 July 25 (Box-folder 009:006)
- Raeburn H. Parker to Joseph Fletcher, 1967July 29 (Box-folder 009:007)
- Olga Von K. Craven to Joseph Fletcher, with attached manuscript, 1967 July 30, 2 Items (Box-folder 009:008)
- H. Crosby Englizian to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 2 (Box-folder 009:009)
- Charles K. Hofling to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 7 (Box-folder 009:010)
- Robert S. Lehman to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 9 (Box-folder 009:011)
- Tom Wilson to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 9 (Box-folder 009:012)
- Robert J. Leuver to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1967 August 10, 2 Items (Box-folder 009:013)
- John to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 11 (Box-folder 009:014)
- Olga [Craven] to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] August 12 (Box-folder 009:015)
- Cora Cunninghame to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 16, 2 Items (Box-folder 009:016)
- Bill [William B. Spofford] to Joseph [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 August 16 (Box-folder 009:017)
- Michael Stephan Kotis to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 17 (Box-folder 009:018)
- Leroy H. Reedy to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 22 (Box-folder 009:019)
- John to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 24 (Box-folder 009:020)
- G. Paul willhite to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 28 (Box-folder 009:021)
- Vern L. Weiss to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 30 (Box-folder 009:022)
- Donald F. Gottschalk to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 August 31 (Box-folder 009:023)
- Beverly Tucker to family and friends, 1967 August 31 (Box-folder 009:024)
- Form letter from Leon P. Loechler, 1967 September 7 (Box-folder 009:025)
- Richard Morford to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 7 (Box-folder 009:026)
- Donald F. Gottschalk to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 8 (Box-folder 009:027)
- Alys M. G. Jones to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 11 (Box-folder 009:028)
- J. Brooke Mosley to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 12 (Box-folder 009:029)
- Eva to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1967] September 12 (Box-folder 009:030)
- Richard F. Hettlinger to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 September 16 (Box-folder 009:031)
- Tom A. Preston to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 21 (Box-folder 009:032)
- Kathy Bell to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 23 (Box-folder 009:033)
- Richard H. Baker, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 26 (Box-folder 009:034)
- Eulah M. Eubank to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 26 (Box-folder 009:035)
- William A. Hobbs to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 September 28 (Box-folder 009:036)
- Shirley Ramming to Episcopal Theological School, 1967 September 28 (Box-folder 009:037)
- Joseph Fletcher to William Hobbs, 1967 September 29 (Box-folder 009:038)
- Dick [Richard H. Baker] to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], [1967 September] (Box-folder 009:039)
- William A. Hobbs to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 2 (Box-folder 009:040)
- R[ichard] H. Baker, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 3 (Box-folder 009:041)
- Oliver Jackson Sands, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 4 (Box-folder 009:042)
- F. Jerone Duderstadt to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 5 (Box-folder 009:043)
- Carroll E. Simcox to Derald Stump, 1967 October 13 (Box-folder 009:044)
- Chuck to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 October 17 (Box-folder 009:045)
- Nickie Leckrone to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 19 (Box-folder 009:046)
- Dave Cumming to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 20 (Box-folder 009:047)
- C. B. Kelley to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosures, 1967 October 22, 6 Items (Box-folder 009:048)
- Richmond Times Dispatch editorial, 1967 October 23, 3 Items (Box-folder 009:049)
- Richard E. Dewey to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 25 (Box-folder 009:050)
- John C. Carnes to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1967 October 26, 3 items (Box-folder 009:051)
- Evelyn G. Tapper to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 29 (Box-folder 009:052)
- Marilyn L.(?) Stahlka to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 October 31 (Box-folder 009:053)
- Mrs. Roland Krause to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 November 3 (Box-folder 009:054)
- Olga Von K. Craven to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 November 4 (Box-folder 009:055)
- John B. Brown to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 November 7 (Box-folder 009:056)
- Wilburn C. Campbell to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 November 7 (Box-folder 009:057)
- Frank L. Smoot to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 November 7 (Box-folder 009:058)
- H. Edward Rowe to F. Sanford Cutler, 1967 November 14 (Box-folder 009:059)
- Mrs. Endres M. Campbell to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 November 15 (Box-folder 009:060)
- Judith Newmark to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 November 15 (Box-folder 009:061)
- Francis C. Huntington to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] November 17 (Box-folder 009:062)
- Joseph Fletcher to John Brown, 1967 November 21 (Box-folder 009:063)
- Celia Matthews to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 November 24 (Box-folder 009:064)
- William E. Smith to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 November 30 (Box-folder 009:065)
- Robert C. Lea, Jr. to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 December 1 (Box-folder 009:066)
- Dick to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 December 9 (Box-folder 009:067)
- Tui Knowling(?) to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 December 12 (Box-folder 009:068)
- Anonymous to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 December 12 (Box-folder 009:069)
- Helen Skerrett to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 December 14 (Box-folder 009:070)
- Clifton K. Meador to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 December 20 (Box-folder 009:071)
- Dana B. Copp to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 December 26 (Box-folder 009:072)
- Anonymous to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 December 26 (Box-folder 009:073)
- William S. Hill to Joseph Fletcher, 1967 December 27 (Box-folder 009:074)
- Arthur E. Walmsley to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1967 December 27 (Box-folder 009:075)
- Patricia McCormick to [Joseph Fletcher], [1967 December] (Box-folder 009:076)
- C. Best to Joseph Fletcher, [1967?] (Box-folder 009:077)
- Edward Bodin, "New Morality," [1967] (Box-folder 009:078)
- Ruth Garland to Joseph Fletcher, [1967?] (Box-folder 009:079)
- Miles J. O. Gullingsrud to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] (Box-folder 009:080)
- Frederick C. Hammond to Joe and Forrest [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher], [1967] (Box-folder 009:081)
- Va. [Mrs. Linus E. Kittredge] to [Joseph and Forrest Fletcher], [1967] (Box-folder 009:082)
- George H. Lawton to [Joseph Fletcher], [1967?] (Box-folder 009:083)
- "Moral Ohne Normen" Joseph Fletcher, (listing for German publisher), 1967 (Box-folder 009:084)
- Buck Talman to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] (Box-folder 009:085)
- Jim Woelfel to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] (Box-folder 009:086)
- Anonymous note to Joseph Fletcher, [1967] (Box-folder 009:087)
- Dorothy Weisback to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 2 (Box-folder 009:088)
- William P. Lehman to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 8 (Box-folder 009:089)
- Edwin G. Wappler to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 11 (Box-folder 009:090)
- James L. Adams to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 12 (Box-folder 009:091)
- Charlie to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1968 January 13 (Box-folder 009:092)
- Stanley Scott Coulter to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], with note from Vera Coulter to Joseph and Forrest Fletcher, 1968 January 14 (Box-folder 009:093)
- F. Bruce Gerhard to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosed manuscript, 1968 January 14, 2 Items (Box-folder 009:094)
- Simon Doniger to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 18 (Box-folder 009:095)
- C. N. Sanford to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 18 (Box-folder 009:096)
- Form letter from Duane R. Miller, 1968 January 19 (Box-folder 009:097)
- Katherine Smith Whitchurch to Joseph Fletcher, with enclosure, 1968 January 22, 2 Items (Box-folder 009:098)
- Leonard M. Sizer to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1968 January 25 (Box-folder 009:099)
- Fred O. Pinkham to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 26 (Box-folder 009:100)
- Charlie to Joe [Joseph Fletcher], 1968 January 29 (Box-folder 009:101)
- Harvey G. Cox to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 30 (Box-folder 009:102)
- Mary Jane Whiteside to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 January 30 (Box-folder 009:103)
- F. Bruce Gerhard to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 3 (Box-folder 009:104)
- Michael A. Meyer to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 4 (Box-folder 009:105)
- C. N. Sanford to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 4 (Box-folder 009:106)
- John L. O'Hear to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 7 (Box-folder 009:107)
- Daniel D. Williams to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 8 (Box-folder 009:108)
- Tom Wilson to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 11 (Box-folder 009:109)
- Marvin Kohl to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 14 (Box-folder 009:110)
- Edward D. Jervey to Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 16 (Box-folder 009:111)
- Citation and Program, Ohio Wesleyan University, Merrick Lectures Convocation, honorary degree conferred on Joseph Fletcher, 1968 February 18 (Box-folder 009:112)